{
    "id": "25aaad46f5434611b5d0298344e5efbe",
    "title": "Confusing adjectives exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "813c61d4223a45529b707502e3bf76ca",
            "title": "Confusing Adjectives Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "At a ………….. date, he became the CEO of the company.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "later",
                        "latter"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I prefer the ………………. proposition to the former.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "later",
                        "latter"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I have an ………………. brother.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "elder",
                        "older",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The niece is ……………… than her uncle.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "elder",
                        "older",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "His …………….. brother serves in the army.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "elder",
                        "older",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "He is the ……………….. member of the club.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "eldest",
                        "oldest",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Broach is ……………… from Bombay than Surat.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "farther",
                        "further"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The ………………. time I saw him he was in high spirits.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "last",
                        "latest"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The ……………… Moghul Emperor came to an ignominious end.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "last",
                        "latest"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The …………….. hospital is two miles from here.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "nearest",
                        "next"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I have a brother. He is ……………. than me.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "older",
                        "elder"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "No ………………… reasons were given.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "further",
                        "farther"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}